var questions = [{
    "question" : "Where is Sri Lanka?",
    "option1" : "West Asia",
    "option2" : "East Eurpoe",
    "option3" : "Middle East",
    "option4" : "South Asia", 
    "answer" :  "4"
},{
    "question" : "What currency is used?",
    "option1" : "Dollar",
    "option2" : "Rupee",
    "option3" : "Dinar",
    "option4" : "Ruble", 
    "answer" :  "2"
},{
    "question" : "Where is the commercial capital of Sri Lanka?",
    "option1" : "Colombo",
    "option2" : "Galle",
    "option3" : "Kandy",
    "option4" : "Matara", 
    "answer" :  "1"
},{
    "question" : "Sigiriya is declared as a world heritage sight by UNESCO. Where is Sigiriya is situated?",
    "option1" : "Kandy",
    "option2" : "Hatton",
    "option3" : "Dambulla",
    "option4" : "Gampola", 
    "answer" :  "3"
},{
    "question" : "When did Sri Lanka achieve home rule, becoming a dominion of the UK?",
    "option1" : "January 1976",
    "option2" : "August 1947",
    "option3" : "August 1945",
    "option4" : "February 1948", 
    "answer" :  "4"
},{
    "question" : "Who did the beat in 1996 to win the Cricket World Cup",
    "option1" : "Australia",
    "option2" : "England",
    "option3" : "South Africa",
    "option4" : "India", 
    "answer" :  "1"
},{
    "question" : "Which of these nations did not rule Sri Lanka?",
    "option1" : "British",
    "option2" : "German",
    "option3" : "Dutch",
    "option4" : "Portugeese", 
    "answer" :  "2"
},{
    "question" : "What is the tallest point of Sri Lanka?",
    "option1" : "Piduruthalagala",
    "option2" : "Adam's Peak",
    "option3" : "Kirigalpotha",
    "option4" : "Hakgala", 
    "answer" :  "1"
},{
    "question" : "What was Sri Lanka formerly known?",
    "option1" : "Nyasaland",
    "option2" : "Dambadiwa",
    "option3" : "Ceylon",
    "option4" : "Hellas", 
    "answer" :  "3"
},{
    "question" : "What seperates Sri Lanka from India?",
    "option1" : "Palk Strait",
    "option2" : "Sunda Strait",
    "option3" : "Davis Strait",
    "option4" : "Malacca Strait", 
    "answer" :  "1"
}]

function increase() {
  var x = document.getElementsByTagName("BODY")[0];
  x.style.fontSize = "large"
}
function decrease() {
  var x = document.getElementsByTagName("BODY")[0];
  x.style.fontSize = "medium"
}


